var questionOne = {
		questionNumber: 1,
		question: 'What was the first game that Mario starred in?',
		correctAnswer: 1,
  		options: ['Mario Bros.', 'Donkey Kong', 'Balloon Fight', 'Marble Madness'],
  		trivia: 'Donkey Kong debuted in arcades in 1981, and at that time Mario was named \"Jumpman.\"',
};

var questionTwo = {
		questionNumber: 2,
		question: 'Who is the main antagonist in the Mario series?',
		correctAnswer: 3,
		options: ['Wario', 'Wart', 'Yoshi', 'Bowser'],
		trivia: 'The fearsome, fire-breathing Bowser is named Koopa in Japan.',
};

var questionThree = {
		questionNumber: 3,
		question: 'What are the fungus-like enemies of the Mario games called?',
		correctAnswer: 2,
		options: ['Toad', 'Funguy', 'Goomba', 'Portabello'],
		trivia: 'The Goomba\'s Japanese name, Kuribo, means \"chestnut guy.\"',
};

var questionFour = {
		questionNumber: 4,
		question: 'What is Mario\'s occupation?',
		correctAnswer: 0,
		options: ['Plumber', 'Archaeologist', 'Mechanic', 'Pizza Deliveryman'],
		trivia: 'In the Super Mario Bros Super Show cartoon, Mario is a plumber from Brooklyn who ends up in the Mushroom Kingdom by way of a magic drain pipe.',
};

var questionFive = {
		questionNumber: 5,
		question: 'In the Mario Kart series, what is the item that shrinks other racers?',
		correctAnswer: 2,
		options: ['Banana Peel', 'Red Shell', 'Lightning Bolt', 'Mushroom'],
		trivia: 'Super Mario Kart debuted on Super Nintendo in 1992, and essentially created the combat-oriented kart-racing video game genre.',
};

var questionSix = {
		questionNumber: 6,
		question: 'What objects does Mario have to collect in Super Mario 64 to advance the game?',
		correctAnswer: 1,
		options: [ 'Coins', 'Stars', 'Mushrooms', 'Eggs'],
		trivia: 'Super Mario 64 (Nintendo 64, 1996) was the first 3D Mario game and set a standard for 3D adventure platform games.',
};

var questionSeven = {
		questionNumber: 7,
		question: 'Mario\'s little brother, Luigi, starred in Luigi\'s Mansion. What console did it debut on in 2001?',
		correctAnswer: 3,
		options: ['Game Boy', 'Virtual Boy', 'Wii', 'GameCube'],
		trivia: 'Luigi first appeared in the 1983 arcade hit Mario Bros., where the titular brothers must exterminate monsters coming from the sewers.',
};

var questionEight = {
		questionNumber: 8,
		question: 'What is Bowser\'s group of mischievous children called?',
		correctAnswer: 0,
		options: ['Koopalings', 'Koopa Klub', 'Turtle Trouble', 'Dinosores'],
		trivia: 'All seven Koopalings are named after famous musicians, and they first appeared in Super Mario Bros. 3 (Nintendo Entertainment System, 1988).',
};

var questionNine = {
		questionNumber: 9,
		question: 'In Super Mario Bros. 3, what animal does Mario turn into in order to fly?',
		correctAnswer: 2,
		options: ['Squirrel', 'Parrot', 'Raccoon', 'Hedgehog'],
		trivia: 'Other animal-themed powers in Super Mario Bros 3 include the Frog suit, which makes swimming in water easier, and the Tanooki suit, which allows the user to transform into an invulnerable statue.',
};

var questionTen = {
		questionNumber: 10,
		question: 'What was Princess Peach\'s official name in North America prior to Super Mario 64?',
		correctAnswer: 1,
		options: ['Princess Zelda', 'Princess Toadstool', 'Princess Pineapple', 'Princess Kate'],
		trivia: 'The starring princess in Super Mario Land (Game Boy, 1989) was named Daisy.',
};

var questionList = [questionOne,questionTwo,questionThree,questionFour,questionFive,questionSix,questionSeven,questionEight,questionNine,questionTen];
